<?xml version="1.0"?>

<agreements>

   <agreement>

      <country>US</country>

      <language>en</language>

      <language_name>English</language_name>

      <publish_date>2014-09-29T20:07:35</publish_date>

      <texts

         xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="chunkedStoredAgreementText">

         <main_title>

            <![CDATA[Ruby Network Services Agreement]]>

         </main_title>

         <agree_text>

            <![CDATA[I Accept]]>

         </agree_text>

         <non_agree_text>

            <![CDATA[I Decline]]>

         </non_agree_text>

         <main_text index="1">

            <![CDATA[This End-User License Agreement (referred to as the "EULA") is a legally binding agreement
between you, the Licensee, an individual customer or entity, and the Ruby Network, the company,
and the author of Ruby, the Software, which may include associated media, printed materials, and
online or electronic documentation. This Agreement is a legally binding contract that includes
terms that limit your legal rights and Licensors' liability to you, and shall govern all access to and
use of the Software. You hereby agree, without limitation or alteration, to all the terms and
conditions contained herein.
By installing, copying, or otherwise using the Product (Ruby), the Licensee agrees to be bound by
the terms and conditions outlined in this EULA. However, if the Licensee does not agree to the
terms and conditions outlined in this EULA, the said Licensee may not download, install, or use
Ruby.
Definitions
 "EULA" shall refer to this End-User-License-Agreement, including any amendment to this
Agreement.
"Licensee" shall refer to the individual or entity that downloads and uses the Software.
"Licensor" shall refer to the company or author, Ruby Network, located at 1 Road Of The Road,
United States 12345.
 "Software/Licensed product" shall mean Ruby, the Licensed Product provided pursuant to this
EULA.
Grant of License
Subject to the terms of this EULA, the Ruby Network hereby grants to the Licensee, a royalty-free,
revocable, limited, non-exclusive license during the term of this EULA to possess and to use a
copy of the Software. The Software is being distributed by Ruby Network. Licensee is not allowed
to make a charge for distributing the Software, either for profit or merely to recover media and
distribution costs.
Intellectual Property
You hereby unconditionally agree that all right, title and interest in the copyrights and other
intellectual property rights in the Licensed Product reside with the Licensor. The trademarks,
logos, designs, and service marks appearing on the Licensed Product are registered and
unregistered marks of the Licensor. Accordingly, nothing in this EULA or the Licensed Product
grants you any right to use any form of intellectual property contained in the Licensed Product.
Therefore, all rights, titles, interests, and copyrights in and/or to the Software, including but not
limited to all images, graphics, animations, audio, video, music, text, data, code, algorithm, and
information, are owned by the Licensor. Accordingly, the Software is protected by all applicable
copyright laws and international treaties, and the Licensee is expected to use the Software
concerning all intellectual property contained therein, except as otherwise provided for in this
EULA.
Description of Rights and Limitations
Installation and Use: Licensee may install and use the Software on a shared computer or
concurrently on different computers, and make multiple back-up copies of the Software, solely for
Licensee's use within Licensee's business or personal use.
Reproduction and Distribution: Licensee may not duplicate or redistribute copies of the
Software, without the Licensors express written permission.
Licensee Limitation: The Licensee may not:
1. Use the Software for any purpose other than personal and non-commercial purposes;
2. Use the Software for any illegal or unlawful purpose;
3. Gather factual content or any other portion of the Software by any automated means,
including but not limited to database scraping or screen scraping; or
4. Reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the Software, except and only to the extent that
such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding the limitation.
Update and Maintenance
Ruby Network shall provide updates and maintenance on a regular basis or as-needed basis.
Support
Ruby Network has no obligation to Software support, or to continue providing or updating any of
the Software.
General Provisions
Termination
In the event of termination, all licenses provided under this EULA shall immediately terminate,
and you agree to discontinue accessing or attempting to access this Licensed product.
Accordingly, this EULA may be:
1. Automatically terminated if the Licensee fails to comply with any of the terms and
conditions under this EULA;
2. Terminated by Ruby Network; or
3. Terminated by the Licensee.
Either Ruby Network or the Licensee may terminate this EULA immediately upon written notice
to the other party, including but not limited to electronic mail.
Non-Transferability
The Licensee has the option to permanently transfer all rights under this EULA, provided the
recipient agrees to the terms of this EULA. Accordingly, this EULA is not assignable or
transferable by the Licensee without the prior written consent of Ruby Network; and any attempt
to do so shall be void.
Notice
Any notice, report, approval or consent required under this EULA shall be in writing and deemed
to have been duly given if delivered by recorded delivery to the respective addresses of the parties.
Integration
Both parties hereby agree that this EULA is the entire and exclusive statement and legal
acknowledgment of the mutual understanding of the parties and supersedes and cancels any
previous written and oral agreement and/or communication relating to the subject matter of this
EULA.
Severability
No delay or failure to exercise, on the part of either party, any privilege, power or rights under this
EULA shall operate as a waiver of any of the terms and provisions of this EULA. Accordingly, no
single or partial exercise of any right under this Agreement shall preclude further exercise of any
other right under this EULA. Suppose any of the outlined provisions of this EULA is deemed to be
unenforceable or invalid in whole or in part by a court of competent jurisdiction. In that case, such
provision shall be limited to the minimum extent necessary for this EULA to remain in full force
and effect and enforceable. The remaining provisions of this Agreement shall not be rendered
unenforceable or invalid. They shall continue to be enforceable and valid in isolation of the
unenforceable and invalid provisions of this EULA.
Warranty and Disclaimer
Ruby Network, and author of the Software, expressly disclaim any warranty for Ruby. The
Licensed Product and all applicable documentation is provided as-is, without warranty of any kind,
whether express or implied, including, without limitation, the implied warranties of
merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. Accordingly, the Licensee
accepts any risk arising out of the use or performance of the Software.
Limited Liability
The Licensee agrees that the Ruby Network shall not be liable to Licensee, or any other related
person or entity claiming any loss of profits, income, savings, or any other consequential,
incidental, special, punitive, direct or indirect damage, whether arising in contract, tort, warranty,
or otherwise. Even if Ruby Network has been advised of the possibility of such damages. These
limitations shall necessarily apply regardless of the primary purpose of any limited remedy. Under
no circumstances shall Ruby Network aggregate liability to the Licensee, or any other person or
entity claiming through the Licensee, exceed the actual monetary amount paid by the Licensee to
Ruby Network for the Software.
Indemnification
You hereby agree to indemnify and hold Ruby Network harmless from and against all liabilities,
damages, losses or expenses, including but not limited to reasonable attorney or other professional
fees in any claim, demand, action or proceeding initiated by any third-party against Ruby Network,
arising from any of your acts, including without limitation, violating this EULA or any other
agreement or any applicable law.
Entire Agreement
This Agreement rightly constitutes the entire understanding between the Ruby Network and the
Licensee and all parties involved. It supersedes all prior agreements of the parties, whether written
or oral, express or implied, statement, condition, or a representation or warranty.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This EULA shall be deemed to be construed under the jurisdiction of the courts located in USA,
without regard to conflicts of laws as regards the provisions thereof. Any legal action relating to
this EULA shall be brought exclusively in the courts of USA, and all parties consent to the
jurisdiction thereof. Furthermore, the prevailing party in any action to enforce this EULA shall be
entitled to recover costs and expenses including, without limitation, legal fees. Accordingly, this
EULA is made within the exclusive jurisdiction of the USA, and its jurisdiction shall supersede
any other jurisdiction of either party's election.]]>

         </main_text>

         <sub_title>

            <![CDATA[Privacy Policy]]>

         </sub_title>

         <sub_text index="1">

            <![CDATA[PRIVACY POLICY

Last updated November 13, 2023



This privacy notice for Ruby Network ("we," "us," or "our"), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share ("process") your information when you use our services ("Services"), such as when you:
Visit our website at Ruby Account Server, or any website of ours that links to this privacy notice
Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events
Questions or concerns? Reading this privacy notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at DISCORD.


SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS

This summary provides key points from our privacy notice, but you can find out more details about any of these topics by clicking the link following each key point or by using our table of contents below to find the section you are looking for.

What personal information do we process? When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process personal information depending on how you interact with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. Learn more about personal information you disclose to us.

Do we process any sensitive personal information? We do not process sensitive personal information.

Do we receive any information from third parties? We do not receive any information from third parties.

How do we process your information? We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent. We process your information only when we have a valid legal reason to do so. Learn more about how we process your information.

In what situations and with which parties do we share personal information? We may share information in specific situations and with specific third parties. Learn more about when and with whom we share your personal information.

How do we keep your information safe? We have organizational and technical processes and procedures in place to protect your personal information. However, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Learn more about how we keep your information safe.

What are your rights? Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean you have certain rights regarding your personal information. Learn more about your privacy rights.

How do you exercise your rights? The easiest way to exercise your rights is by visiting , or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

Want to learn more about what we do with any information we collect? Review the privacy notice in full.


TABLE OF CONTENTS

1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
2. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?
3. WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
4. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
5. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
6. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?
7. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?
8. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES
9. DO UNITED STATES RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?
10. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?
11. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?
12. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?


1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

Personal information you disclose to us

In Short: We collect personal information that you provide to us.

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Services, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us.

Personal Information Provided by You. The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:
usernames
passwords
email addresses
Sensitive Information. We do not process sensitive information.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

2. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?

In Short: We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent.

We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:
To facilitate account creation and authentication and otherwise manage user accounts. We may process your information so you can create and log in to your account, as well as keep your account in working order.




To save or protect an individual's vital interest. We may process your information when necessary to save or protect an individual’s vital interest, such as to prevent harm.

3. WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?

In Short: We only process your personal information when we believe it is necessary and we have a valid legal reason (i.e., legal basis) to do so under applicable law, like with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services to enter into or fulfill our contractual obligations, to protect your rights, or to fulfill our legitimate business interests.

If you are located in the EU or UK, this section applies to you.

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and UK GDPR require us to explain the valid legal bases we rely on in order to process your personal information. As such, we may rely on the following legal bases to process your personal information:
Consent. We may process your information if you have given us permission (i.e., consent) to use your personal information for a specific purpose. You can withdraw your consent at any time. Learn more about withdrawing your consent.
Legal Obligations. We may process your information where we believe it is necessary for compliance with our legal obligations, such as to cooperate with a law enforcement body or regulatory agency, exercise or defend our legal rights, or disclose your information as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.
Vital Interests. We may process your information where we believe it is necessary to protect your vital interests or the vital interests of a third party, such as situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person.

If you are located in Canada, this section applies to you.

We may process your information if you have given us specific permission (i.e., express consent) to use your personal information for a specific purpose, or in situations where your permission can be inferred (i.e., implied consent). You can withdraw your consent at any time.

In some exceptional cases, we may be legally permitted under applicable law to process your information without your consent, including, for example:
If collection is clearly in the interests of an individual and consent cannot be obtained in a timely way
For investigations and fraud detection and prevention
For business transactions provided certain conditions are met
If it is contained in a witness statement and the collection is necessary to assess, process, or settle an insurance claim
For identifying injured, ill, or deceased persons and communicating with next of kin
If we have reasonable grounds to believe an individual has been, is, or may be victim of financial abuse
If it is reasonable to expect collection and use with consent would compromise the availability or the accuracy of the information and the collection is reasonable for purposes related to investigating a breach of an agreement or a contravention of the laws of Canada or a province
If disclosure is required to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or rules of the court relating to the production of records
If it was produced by an individual in the course of their employment, business, or profession and the collection is consistent with the purposes for which the information was produced
If the collection is solely for journalistic, artistic, or literary purposes
If the information is publicly available and is specified by the regulations

4. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

In Short: We may share information in specific situations described in this section and/or with the following third parties.

We may need to share your personal information in the following situations:
Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

5. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law.

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than   the period of time in which users have an account with us.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

6. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?

In Short: We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical security measures.

We have implemented appropriate and reasonable technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.

7. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?

In Short: In some regions, such as the European Economic Area (EEA), United Kingdom (UK), Switzerland, and Canada, you have rights that allow you greater access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time.

In some regions (like the EEA, UK, Switzerland, and Canada), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; (iv) if applicable, to data portability; and (v) not to be subject to automated decision-making. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. You can make such a request by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section "HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?" below.

We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.
 
If you are located in the EEA or UK and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your Member State data protection authority or UK data protection authority.

If you are located in Switzerland, you may contact the Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner.

Withdrawing your consent: If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, which may be express and/or implied consent depending on the applicable law, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section "HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?" below or updating your preferences.

However, please note that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal nor, when applicable law allows, will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

Account Information

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:
Log in to your account settings and update your user account.
Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our legal terms and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at DISCORD.

8. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

9. DO UNITED STATES RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?

In Short: If you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information.

What categories of personal information do we collect?

We have collected the following categories of personal information in the past twelve (12) months:

Category	Examples	Collected
A. Identifiers
Contact details, such as real name, alias, postal address, telephone or mobile contact number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, and account name

NO

B. Personal information as defined in the California Customer Records statute
Name, contact information, education, employment, employment history, and financial information

NO

C. Protected classification characteristics under state or federal law
Gender and date of birth

NO

D. Commercial information
Transaction information, purchase history, financial details, and payment information

NO

E. Biometric information
Fingerprints and voiceprints

NO

F. Internet or other similar network activity
Browsing history, search history, online behavior, interest data, and interactions with our and other websites, applications, systems, and advertisements

NO

G. Geolocation data
Device location

NO

H. Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
Images and audio, video or call recordings created in connection with our business activities

NO

I. Professional or employment-related information
Business contact details in order to provide you our Services at a business level or job title, work history, and professional qualifications if you apply for a job with us

NO

J. Education Information
Student records and directory information

NO

K. Inferences drawn from collected personal information
Inferences drawn from any of the collected personal information listed above to create a profile or summary about, for example, an individual’s preferences and characteristics

NO

L. Sensitive personal Information		

NO


We will use and retain the collected personal information as needed to provide the Services or for:
Category B - As long as the user has an account with us
We may also collect other personal information outside of these categories through instances where you interact with us in person, online, or by phone or mail in the context of:
Receiving help through our customer support channels;
Participation in customer surveys or contests; and
Facilitation in the delivery of our Services and to respond to your inquiries.
How do we use and share your personal information?

Learn about how we use your personal information in the section, "HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?"

Will your information be shared with anyone else?

We may disclose your personal information with our service providers pursuant to a written contract between us and each service provider. Learn more about how we disclose personal information to in the section, "WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?"

We may use your personal information for our own business purposes, such as for undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration. This is not considered to be "selling" of your personal information.

We have not disclosed, sold, or shared any personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months. We will not sell or share personal information in the future belonging to website visitors, users, and other consumers.

California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g., backups, etc.).

CCPA Privacy Notice

This section applies only to California residents. Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), you have the rights listed below.

The California Code of Regulations defines a "residents" as:

(1) every individual who is in the State of California for other than a temporary or transitory purpose and
(2) every individual who is domiciled in the State of California who is outside the State of California for a temporary or transitory purpose

All other individuals are defined as "non-residents."

If this definition of "resident" applies to you, we must adhere to certain rights and obligations regarding your personal information.

Your rights with respect to your personal data

Right to request deletion of the data — Request to delete

You can ask for the deletion of your personal information. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will respect your request and delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as (but not limited to) the exercise by another consumer of his or her right to free speech, our compliance requirements resulting from a legal obligation, or any processing that may be required to protect against illegal activities.

Right to be informed — Request to know

Depending on the circumstances, you have a right to know:
whether we collect and use your personal information;
the categories of personal information that we collect;
the purposes for which the collected personal information is used;
whether we sell or share personal information to third parties;
the categories of personal information that we sold, shared, or disclosed for a business purpose;
the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, shared, or disclosed for a business purpose;
the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information; and
the specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
In accordance with applicable law, we are not obligated to provide or delete consumer information that is de-identified in response to a consumer request or to re-identify individual data to verify a consumer request.

Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights

We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information

We do not process consumer's sensitive personal information.

Verification process

Upon receiving your request, we will need to verify your identity to determine you are the same person about whom we have the information in our system. These verification efforts require us to ask you to provide information so that we can match it with information you have previously provided us. For instance, depending on the type of request you submit, we may ask you to provide certain information so that we can match the information you provide with the information we already have on file, or we may contact you through a communication method (e.g., phone or email) that you have previously provided to us. We may also use other verification methods as the circumstances dictate.

We will only use personal information provided in your request to verify your identity or authority to make the request. To the extent possible, we will avoid requesting additional information from you for the purposes of verification. However, if we cannot verify your identity from the information already maintained by us, we may request that you provide additional information for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes. We will delete such additionally provided information as soon as we finish verifying you.

Other privacy rights
You may object to the processing of your personal information.
You may request correction of your personal data if it is incorrect or no longer relevant, or ask to restrict the processing of the information.
You can designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent that does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf in accordance with the CCPA.
You may request to opt out from future selling or sharing of your personal information to third parties. Upon receiving an opt-out request, we will act upon the request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than fifteen (15) days from the date of the request submission.
To exercise these rights, you can contact us by visiting , DMing an admin on Ruby , or by referring to the contact details at the bottom of this document. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.

10. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?

In Short: Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated "Revised" date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

11. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at dm an Ruby admin on the app or discord server or contact us by post at:

Ruby Network
123 STREET OF RUBY
124 STREET OF RUBY
USA, NY 53842
United States

12. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?

You have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please visit: .]]>

         </sub_text>

      </texts>

      <type>NINTENDO-NETWORK-EULA</type>

      <version>0300</version>

   </agreement>

   <agreement>

      <country>US</country>

      <language>en</language>

      <language_name>Español</language_name>

      <publish_date>201-09-29T20:07:35</publish_date>

      <texts

         xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="chunkedStoredAgreementText">

         <main_title>

            <![CDATA[Ruby Network Services Agreement]]>

         </main_title>

         <agree_text>

            <![CDATA[Acepto]]>

         </agree_text>

         <non_agree_text>

            <![CDATA[Renuncio]>

         </non_agree_text>

         <main_text index="1">

            <![CDATA[Este Acuerdo de licencia de usuario final (denominado "CLUF") es un acuerdo legalmente vinculante
entre usted, el Licenciatario, un cliente individual o entidad, y Ruby Network, la empresa,
y el autor de Ruby, el Software, que puede incluir medios asociados, materiales impresos y
documentación en línea o electrónica. Este Acuerdo es un contrato legalmente vinculante que incluye
términos que limitan sus derechos legales y la responsabilidad de los Licenciantes hacia usted, y regirán todo acceso y
uso del Software. Por la presente usted acepta, sin limitación ni alteración, todos los términos y
condiciones aquí contenidas.
Al instalar, copiar o utilizar de otro modo el Producto (Ruby), el Licenciatario acepta estar sujeto a
los términos y condiciones descritos en este CLUF. Sin embargo, si el Licenciatario no está de acuerdo con el
términos y condiciones descritos en este CLUF, dicho Licenciatario no puede descargar, instalar o utilizar
Rubí.
Definiciones
  "CLUF" se referirá a este Acuerdo de licencia de usuario final, incluida cualquier enmienda a este
Acuerdo.
"Licenciatario" se referirá a la persona o entidad que descarga y utiliza el Software.
"Licenciante" se referirá a la empresa o autor, Ruby Network, ubicada en 1 Road Of The Road,
Estados Unidos 12345.
  "Software/Producto con licencia" significará Ruby, el Producto con licencia proporcionado de conformidad con este
CLUF.
Concesión de la licencia
Sujeto a los términos de este CLUF, Ruby Network otorga al Licenciatario, libre de regalías,
Licencia revocable, limitada y no exclusiva durante la vigencia de este CLUF para poseer y utilizar un
copia del software. El software lo distribuye Ruby Network. El licenciatario no está permitido
cobrar por la distribución del Software, ya sea con fines de lucro o simplemente para recuperar medios y
costos de distribución.
Propiedad intelectual
Por la presente, usted acepta incondicionalmente que todos los derechos, títulos e intereses sobre los derechos de autor y otros
Los derechos de propiedad intelectual del Producto con licencia residen en el Licenciante. Las marcas registradas,
Los logotipos, diseños y marcas de servicio que aparecen en el Producto con licencia están registrados y
marcas no registradas del Licenciante. En consecuencia, nada en este CLUF o el Producto Licenciado
le otorga cualquier derecho a utilizar cualquier forma de propiedad intelectual contenida en el Producto con licencia.
Por lo tanto, todos los derechos, títulos, intereses y derechos de autor sobre el Software, incluidos, entre otros,
limitado a todas las imágenes, gráficos, animaciones, audio, vídeo, música, texto, datos, código, algoritmo y
información, son propiedad del Licenciante. En consecuencia, el Software está protegido por todas las leyes aplicables.
leyes de derechos de autor y tratados internacionales, y se espera que el Licenciatario utilice el Software
en relación con toda la propiedad intelectual contenida en el mismo, salvo que se disponga lo contrario en este
CLUF.
Descripción de derechos y limitaciones
Instalación y uso: el Licenciatario puede instalar y utilizar el Software en una computadora compartida o
simultáneamente en diferentes computadoras y realizar múltiples copias de seguridad del Software, únicamente para
Uso del Licenciatario dentro de su negocio o uso personal.
Reproducción y distribución: el licenciatario no puede duplicar ni redistribuir copias del
Software, sin el permiso expreso por escrito de los Licenciantes.
Limitación del Licenciatario: El Licenciatario no podrá:
1. Utilizar el Software para cualquier fin que no sea personal y no comercial;
2. Usar el Software para cualquier propósito ilegal o ilícito;
3. Recopilar contenido factual o cualquier otra parte del Software por cualquier medio automatizado,
incluido, entre otros, el raspado de bases de datos o el raspado de pantalla; o
4. Realizar ingeniería inversa, descompilar o desensamblar el Software, excepto y solo en la medida en que
dicha actividad está expresamente permitida por la ley aplicable a pesar de la limitación.
Actualización y mantenimiento
Ruby Network proporcionará actualizaciones y mantenimiento de forma regular o según sea necesario.
Apoyo
Ruby Network no tiene ninguna obligación de brindar soporte de software, ni de continuar proporcionando o actualizando cualquiera de
El software.
Provisiones generales
Terminación
En caso de rescisión, todas las licencias proporcionadas en virtud de este CLUF rescindirán inmediatamente,
y usted acepta dejar de acceder o intentar acceder a este producto con licencia.
En consecuencia, este EULA puede ser:
1. Terminado automáticamente si el Licenciatario incumple cualquiera de los términos y
condiciones bajo este CLUF;
2. Terminado por Ruby Network; o
3. Rescindido por el Licenciatario.
Ruby Network o el Licenciatario pueden rescindir este EULA inmediatamente mediante notificación por escrito.
a la otra parte, incluido, entre otros, el correo electrónico.
Intransferibilidad
El Licenciatario tiene la opción de transferir permanentemente todos los derechos bajo este CLUF, siempre que el
El destinatario acepta los términos de este CLUF. En consecuencia, este CLUF no es transferible ni
transferible por el Licenciatario sin el consentimiento previo por escrito de Ruby Network; y cualquier intento
hacerlo será nulo.
Aviso
Cualquier notificación, informe, aprobación o consentimiento requerido según este CLUF se realizará por escrito y se considerará
haber sido debidamente entregado si se entregó mediante entrega certificada a las direcciones respectivas de las partes.
Integración
Ambas partes acuerdan que este CLUF es la declaración completa y exclusiva y legal
reconocimiento del entendimiento mutuo de las partes y reemplaza y cancela cualquier
acuerdo y/o comunicación previa escrita y oral relacionada con el tema de este
CLUF.
Divisibilidad
Ninguna demora o falta de ejercicio, por parte de cualquiera de las partes, de cualquier privilegio, poder o derecho bajo este
EULA operará como una renuncia a cualquiera de los términos y disposiciones de este EULA. En consecuencia, no
El ejercicio único o parcial de cualquier derecho en virtud de este Acuerdo impedirá el ejercicio posterior de cualquier
otro derecho bajo este CLUF. Supongamos que alguna de las disposiciones descritas en este CLUF se considera
inaplicable o inválida en su totalidad o en parte por un tribunal de jurisdicción competente. En ese caso, tal
La disposición se limitará al mínimo necesario para que este CLUF permanezca en plena vigencia.
y efecto y ejecutable. Las disposiciones restantes de este Acuerdo no se considerarán
inaplicable o inválido. Seguirán siendo exigibles y válidos independientemente del
disposiciones inaplicables e inválidas de este CLUF.
Garantía y descargo de responsabilidad
Ruby Network y autor del Software renuncian expresamente a cualquier garantía para Ruby. El
El producto con licencia y toda la documentación aplicable se proporcionan tal cual, sin garantía de ningún tipo,
ya sea expresa o implícita, incluidas, entre otras, las garantías implícitas de
comerciabilidad, idoneidad para un propósito particular o no infracción. En consecuencia, el licenciatario
acepta cualquier riesgo que surja del uso o desempeño del Software.
De responsabilidad limitada
El Licenciatario acepta que Ruby Network no será responsable ante el Licenciatario ni ante ningún otro
persona o entidad que reclame cualquier pérdida de ganancias, ingresos, ahorros o cualquier otra consecuencia,
daño incidental, especial, punitivo, directo o indirecto, ya sea que surja de contrato, agravio, garantía,
o de otro modo. Incluso si Ruby Network ha sido advertida de la posibilidad de tales daños. Estos
Las limitaciones se aplicarán necesariamente independientemente del propósito principal de cualquier recurso limitado. Bajo
En ningún caso Ruby Network agregará responsabilidad al Licenciatario, ni a ninguna otra persona o
entidad que reclama a través del Licenciatario, excede el monto monetario real pagado por el Licenciatario a
Red Ruby para el software.
Indemnización
Por la presente, usted acepta indemnizar y eximir a Ruby Network de toda responsabilidad,
daños, pérdidas o gastos, incluidos, entre otros, abogados razonables u otros profesionales
honorarios en cualquier reclamo, demanda, acción o procedimiento iniciado por cualquier tercero contra Ruby Network,
que surja de cualquiera de sus actos, incluido, entre otros, la violación de este CLUF o cualquier otro
acuerdo o cualquier ley aplicable.
Acuerdo completo
Este Acuerdo constituye correctamente el entendimiento completo entre Ruby Network y la
Licenciatario y todas las partes involucradas. Reemplaza todos los acuerdos anteriores de las partes, ya sean escritos
u oral, expresa o implícita, declaración, condición o representación o garantía.
Ley aplicable y jurisdicción
Este CLUF se considerará interpretado bajo la jurisdicción de los tribunales ubicados en EE. UU.,
sin tener en cuenta conflictos de leyes en lo que respecta a sus disposiciones. Cualquier acción legal relacionada con
Este CLUF se presentará exclusivamente en los tribunales de EE. UU. y todas las partes consienten en
jurisdicción del mismo. Además, la parte que prevalezca en cualquier acción para hacer cumplir este CLUF será
tiene derecho a recuperar costos y gastos, incluidos, entre otros, honorarios legales. En consecuencia, este
EULA se elabora dentro de la jurisdicción exclusiva de los EE. UU., y su jurisdicción reemplazará
cualquier otra jurisdicción de elección de cualquiera de las partes. ]]>

         </main_text>

         <sub_title>

            <![CDATA[Privacy Policy]]>

         </sub_title>

         <sub_text index="1">

            <![CDATA[POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD

Última actualización 13 de noviembre de 2023



Este aviso de privacidad para Ruby Network ("nosotros", "nos" o "nuestro") describe cómo y por qué podemos recopilar, almacenar, usar y/o compartir ("procesar") su información cuando utiliza nuestros servicios ( "Servicios"), como cuando usted:
Visite nuestro sitio web en Ruby Account Server, o cualquier sitio web nuestro que tenga enlace a este aviso de privacidad.
Interactuar con nosotros de otras formas relacionadas, incluidas ventas, marketing o eventos.
¿Preguntas o inquietudes? Leer este aviso de privacidad le ayudará a comprender sus derechos y opciones de privacidad. Si no está de acuerdo con nuestras políticas y prácticas, no utilice nuestros Servicios. Si aún tiene alguna pregunta o inquietud, comuníquese con nosotros en DISCORD.


RESUMEN DE PUNTOS CLAVE

Este resumen proporciona puntos clave de nuestro aviso de privacidad, pero puede encontrar más detalles sobre cualquiera de estos temas haciendo clic en el enlace que sigue a cada punto clave o utilizando nuestra tabla de contenido a continuación para encontrar la sección que está buscando.

¿Qué datos personales procesamos? Cuando visita, utiliza o navega por nuestros Servicios, podemos procesar información personal dependiendo de cómo interactúa con nosotros y los Servicios, las elecciones que realiza y los productos y funciones que utiliza. Obtenga más información sobre la información personal que nos revela.

¿Procesamos alguna información personal sensible? No procesamos información personal sensible.

¿Recibimos alguna información de terceros? No recibimos ninguna información de terceros.

¿Cómo procesamos su información? Procesamos su información para proporcionar, mejorar y administrar nuestros Servicios, comunicarnos con usted, por motivos de seguridad y prevención de fraude, y para cumplir con la ley. También podemos procesar su información para otros fines con su consentimiento. Procesamos su información solo cuando tenemos una razón legal válida para hacerlo. Obtenga más información sobre cómo procesamos su información.

¿En qué situaciones y con qué partes compartimos información personal? Podemos compartir información en situaciones específicas y con terceros específicos. Obtenga más información sobre cuándo y con quién compartimos su información personal.

¿Cómo mantenemos segura su información? Contamos con procesos y procedimientos organizativos y técnicos para proteger su información personal. Sin embargo, no se puede garantizar que ninguna transmisión electrónica a través de Internet o tecnología de almacenamiento de información sea 100% segura, por lo que no podemos prometer ni garantizar que los piratas informáticos, ciberdelincuentes u otros terceros no autorizados no puedan vulnerar nuestra seguridad y recopilar, acceder de manera inadecuada. , robar o modificar su información. Obtenga más información sobre cómo mantenemos su información segura.

¿Cuales son tus derechos? Dependiendo de dónde se encuentre geográficamente, la ley de privacidad aplicable puede significar que tiene ciertos derechos con respecto a su información personal. Obtenga más información sobre sus derechos de privacidad.

¿Cómo ejerce sus derechos? La forma más sencilla de ejercer sus derechos es visitando o poniéndose en contacto con nosotros. Consideraremos y actuaremos ante cualquier solicitud de acuerdo con las leyes de protección de datos aplicables.

¿Quiere obtener más información sobre lo que hacemos con la información que recopilamos? Revise el aviso de privacidad en su totalidad.


TABLA DE CONTENIDO

1. ¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN RECOGEMOS?
2. ¿CÓMO PROCESAMOS TU INFORMACIÓN?
3. ¿EN QUÉ BASES LEGALES NOS BASAMOS PARA TRATAR TU INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?
4. ¿CUÁNDO Y CON QUIÉN COMPARTIMOS TU INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?
5. ¿CUÁNTO TIEMPO CONSERVAMOS TU INFORMACIÓN?
6. ¿CÓMO MANTENEMOS SU INFORMACIÓN SEGURA?
7. ¿CUÁLES SON TUS DERECHOS DE PRIVACIDAD?
8. CONTROLES PARA FUNCIONES DE NO SEGUIMIENTO
9. ¿TIENEN LOS RESIDENTES DE ESTADOS UNIDOS DERECHOS DE PRIVACIDAD ESPECÍFICOS?
10. ¿ACTUALIZAMOS ESTE AVISO?
11. ¿CÓMO PUEDE CONTACTARNOS SOBRE ESTE AVISO?
12. ¿CÓMO PUEDES REVISAR, ACTUALIZAR O ELIMINAR LOS DATOS QUE RECOPILAMOS DE TI?


1. ¿QUÉ INFORMACIÓN RECOGEMOS?

Información personal que usted nos revela

En resumen: recopilamos la información personal que usted nos proporciona.

Recopilamos información personal que usted nos proporciona voluntariamente cuando se registra en los Servicios, expresa interés en obtener información sobre nosotros o nuestros productos y Servicios, cuando participa en actividades en los Servicios o cuando se comunica con nosotros.

Información personal proporcionada por usted. La información personal que recopilamos depende del contexto de sus interacciones con nosotros y los Servicios, las elecciones que haga y los productos y funciones que utilice. La información personal que recopilamos puede incluir lo siguiente:
nombres de usuario
contraseñas
correos electrónicos
Información sensible. No procesamos información sensible.

Toda la información personal que nos proporcione debe ser verdadera, completa y precisa, y debe notificarnos cualquier cambio en dicha información personal.

2. ¿CÓMO PROCESAMOS TU INFORMACIÓN?

En resumen: procesamos su información para proporcionar, mejorar y administrar nuestros Servicios, comunicarnos con usted, por motivos de seguridad y prevención de fraude, y para cumplir con la ley. También podemos procesar su información para otros fines con su consentimiento.

Nosotros procesamos su información personal por diversos motivos, dependiendo de cómo interactúa con nuestros Servicios, que incluyen:
Para facilitar la creación y autenticación de cuentas y administrar cuentas de usuario. Podemos procesar su información para que pueda crear e iniciar sesión en su cuenta, así como mantener su cuenta en funcionamiento.




Para salvar o proteger el interés vital de un individuo. Podemos procesar su información cuando sea necesario para salvar o proteger el interés vital de un individuo, como por ejemplo para evitar daños.

3. ¿EN QUÉ BASES LEGALES NOS BASAMOS PARA TRATAR TU INFORMACIÓN?

En resumen: solo procesamos su información personal cuando creemos que es necesaria y tenemos una razón legal válida (es decir, base legal) para hacerlo según la ley aplicable, como con su consentimiento, para cumplir con las leyes, para brindarle servicios. para celebrar o cumplir nuestras obligaciones contractuales, proteger sus derechos o cumplir nuestros intereses comerciales legítimos.

Si se encuentra en la UE o el Reino Unido, esta sección se aplica a usted.

El Reglamento General de Protección de Datos (GDPR) y el GDPR del Reino Unido nos exigen que expliquemos las bases legales válidas en las que nos basamos para procesar su información personal. Como tal, podemos basarnos en las siguientes bases legales para procesar su información personal:
Consentir. Podemos procesar su información si nos ha dado permiso (es decir, consentimiento) para usar su información personal para un propósito específico. Puede retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento. Obtenga más información sobre cómo retirar su consentimiento.
Obligaciones legales. Podemos procesar su información cuando creamos que es necesario para cumplir con nuestras obligaciones legales, como cooperar con un organismo encargado de hacer cumplir la ley o una agencia reguladora, ejercer o defender nuestros derechos legales, o divulgar su información como prueba en un litigio en el que estemos. involucrado.
Intereses vitales. Podemos procesar su información cuando creamos que es necesario para proteger sus intereses vitales o los intereses vitales de un tercero, como situaciones que involucran amenazas potenciales a la seguridad de cualquier persona.

Si se encuentra en Canadá, esta sección se aplica a usted.

Podemos procesar su información si nos ha dado permiso específico (es decir, consentimiento expreso) para usar su información personal para un propósito específico, o en situaciones en las que se puede inferir su permiso (es decir, consentimiento implícito). Puede retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento.

En algunos casos excepcionales, es posible que la ley aplicable nos permita procesar su información sin su consentimiento, incluidos, por ejemplo:
Si la recopilación redunda claramente en beneficio de un individuo y no se puede obtener el consentimiento de manera oportuna
Para investigaciones y detección y prevención de fraudes.
Para transacciones comerciales siempre que se cumplan ciertas condiciones.
Si está contenido en una declaración de un testigo y el cobro es necesario para evaluar, procesar o resolver un reclamo de seguro.
Para identificar personas heridas, enfermas o fallecidas y comunicarse con los familiares más cercanos
Si tenemos motivos razonables para creer que una persona ha sido, es o puede ser víctima de abuso financiero
Si es razonable esperar que la recopilación y el uso con consentimiento comprometan la disponibilidad o la exactitud de la información y la recopilación es razonable para fines relacionados con la investigación de un incumplimiento de un acuerdo o una contravención de las leyes de Canadá o de una provincia.
Si se requiere la divulgación para cumplir con una citación, orden judicial, orden judicial o reglas del tribunal relacionadas con la producción de registros
Si fue producida por un individuo en el curso de su empleo, negocio o profesión y la recopilación es consistente con los propósitos para los cuales se produjo la información.
Si la colección tiene como único fin periodístico, artístico o literario
Si la información está disponible públicamente y está especificada por la normativa.

4. ¿CUÁNDO Y CON QUIÉN COMPARTIMOS TU INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?

En resumen: podemos compartir información en situaciones específicas descritas en esta sección y/o con los siguientes terceros.

Es posible que necesitemos compartir su información personal en las siguientes situaciones:
Transferencias de Negocios. Podemos compartir o transferir su información en relación con, o durante las negociaciones de, cualquier fusión, venta de activos de la empresa, financiación o adquisición de todo o una parte de nuestro negocio a otra empresa.

5. ¿CUÁNTO TIEMPO CONSERVAMOS TU INFORMACIÓN?

En resumen: conservamos su información durante el tiempo necesario para cumplir con los fines descritos en este aviso de privacidad, a menos que la ley exija lo contrario.

Solo conservaremos su información personal durante el tiempo que sea necesario para los fines establecidos en este aviso de privacidad, a menos que la ley exija o permita un período de retención más prolongado (como requisitos fiscales, contables u otros requisitos legales). Ningún propósito de este aviso requerirá que conservemos su información personal por más tiempo que el período de tiempo en el que los usuarios tienen una cuenta con nosotros.

Cuando no tengamos una necesidad comercial legítima y continua de procesar su información personal, lo haremos Luego eliminaremos o anonimizaremos dicha información o, si esto no es posible (por ejemplo, porque su información personal se ha almacenado en archivos de respaldo), almacenaremos de forma segura su información personal y la aislaremos de cualquier procesamiento posterior hasta que sea posible su eliminación.

6. ¿CÓMO MANTENEMOS SU INFORMACIÓN SEGURA?

En resumen: nuestro objetivo es proteger su información personal a través de un sistema de medidas de seguridad técnicas y organizativas.

Hemos implementado medidas de seguridad técnicas y organizativas apropiadas y razonables diseñadas para proteger la seguridad de cualquier información personal que procesamos. Sin embargo, a pesar de nuestras medidas de seguridad y esfuerzos para proteger su información, no se puede garantizar que ninguna transmisión electrónica a través de Internet o tecnología de almacenamiento de información sea 100% segura, por lo que no podemos prometer ni garantizar que los piratas informáticos, ciberdelincuentes u otros terceros no autorizados no serán capaz de burlar nuestra seguridad y recopilar, acceder, robar o modificar indebidamente su información. Aunque haremos todo lo posible para proteger su información personal, la transmisión de información personal hacia y desde nuestros Servicios es bajo su propio riesgo. Sólo debe acceder a los Servicios dentro de un entorno seguro.

7. ¿CUÁLES SON TUS DERECHOS DE PRIVACIDAD?

En resumen: en algunas regiones, como el Espacio Económico Europeo (EEE), el Reino Unido (Reino Unido), Suiza y Canadá, usted tiene derechos que le permiten un mayor acceso y control sobre su información personal. Puede revisar, cambiar o cancelar su cuenta en cualquier momento.

En algunas regiones (como el EEE, el Reino Unido, Suiza y Canadá), usted tiene ciertos derechos según las leyes de protección de datos aplicables. Estos pueden incluir el derecho (i) a solicitar acceso y obtener una copia de su información personal, (ii) a solicitar rectificación o eliminación; (iii) restringir el procesamiento de su información personal; (iv) en su caso, a la portabilidad de los datos; y (v) no estar sujeto a la toma de decisiones automatizada. En determinadas circunstancias, también puede tener derecho a oponerse al procesamiento de su información personal. Puede realizar dicha solicitud comunicándose con nosotros utilizando los datos de contacto proporcionados en la sección "¿CÓMO PUEDE CONTACTARNOS SOBRE ESTE AVISO?" abajo.

Consideraremos y actuaremos ante cualquier solicitud de acuerdo con las leyes de protección de datos aplicables.
 
Si se encuentra en el EEE o el Reino Unido y cree que estamos procesando ilegalmente su información personal, también tiene derecho a presentar una queja ante la autoridad de protección de datos de su Estado miembro o ante la autoridad de protección de datos del Reino Unido.

Si se encuentra en Suiza, puede ponerse en contacto con el Comisionado Federal de Información y Protección de Datos.

Retirar su consentimiento: si confiamos en su consentimiento para procesar su información personal, que puede ser un consentimiento expreso y/o implícito según la ley aplicable, tiene derecho a retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento. Puede retirar su consentimiento en cualquier momento poniéndose en contacto con nosotros utilizando los datos de contacto proporcionados en la sección "¿CÓMO PUEDE CONTACTARNOS SOBRE ESTE AVISO?" a continuación o actualizando tus preferencias.

Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que esto no afectará la legalidad del procesamiento antes de su retiro ni, cuando la ley aplicable lo permita, afectará el procesamiento de su información personal realizado basándose en motivos de procesamiento legales distintos del consentimiento.

Información de la cuenta

Si en algún momento desea revisar o cambiar la información de su cuenta o cancelarla, puede:
Inicie sesión en la configuración de su cuenta y actualice su cuenta de usuario.
Si solicita cancelar su cuenta, desactivaremos o eliminaremos su cuenta y su información de nuestras bases de datos activas. Sin embargo, podemos conservar cierta información en nuestros archivos para evitar fraudes, solucionar problemas, ayudar con cualquier investigación, hacer cumplir nuestros términos legales y/o cumplir con los requisitos legales aplicables.

Si tiene preguntas o comentarios sobre sus derechos de privacidad, puede enviarnos un correo electrónico a DISCORD.

8. CONTROLES PARA FUNCIONES DE NO SEGUIMIENTO

La mayoría de los navegadores web y algunos sistemas operativos y aplicaciones móviles incluyen una función o configuración de No rastrear ("DNT") que puede activar para indicar su preferencia de privacidad y no monitorear ni recopilar datos sobre sus actividades de navegación en línea. En esta etapa no se ha finalizado ningún estándar tecnológico uniforme para reconocer e implementar señales DNT. Como tal, actualmente no respondemos a las señales del navegador DNT ni a ningún otro mecanismo que comunique automáticamente su elección de no ser rastreado en línea. Si se adopta un estándar para el seguimiento en línea que debamos seguir en el futuro, le informaremos sobre esa práctica en una versión revisada de este aviso de privacidad.

9. ¿TIENEN LOS RESIDENTES DE ESTADOS UNIDOS DERECHOS DE PRIVACIDAD ESPECÍFICOS?

En resumen: si es residente de California, se le otorgan derechos específicos con respecto al acceso a su información personal.

¿Qué categorías de información personal recopilamos?

Hemos recopilado las siguientes categorías de información personal en los últimos doce (12) meses:

Ejemplos de categorías recopilados
A. Identificadores
Detalles de contacto, como nombre real, alias, dirección postal, número de contacto telefónico o móvil, identificador personal único, identificador en línea, dirección de protocolo de Internet, dirección de correo electrónico y nombre de cuenta.

NO

B. Información personal según se define en el estatuto de Registros de clientes de California
Nombre, información de contacto, educación, empleo, historial laboral e información financiera.

NO

C. Características de clasificación protegidas según la ley estatal o federal
Género y fecha de nacimiento.

NO

D. Información comercial
Información de transacciones, historial de compras, detalles financieros e información de pago.

NO

E. Información biométrica
Huellas dactilares y de voz

NO

F. Internet u otra actividad de red similar
Historial de navegación, historial de búsqueda, comportamiento en línea, datos de interés e interacciones con nuestros sitios web, aplicaciones, sistemas y anuncios y otros

NO

G. Datos de geolocalización
Ubicación del dispositivo

NO

H. Información de audio, electrónica, visual, térmica, olfativa o similar
Imágenes y grabaciones de audio, vídeo o llamadas creadas en relación con nuestras actividades comerciales.

NO

I. Información profesional o laboral
Datos de contacto comercial para brindarle nuestros Servicios a nivel comercial o puesto de trabajo, historial laboral y calificaciones profesionales si solicita un trabajo con nosotros.

NO

J. Información educativa
Registros estudiantiles e información del directorio

NO

K. Inferencias extraídas de la información personal recopilada
Inferencias extraídas de cualquiera de la información personal recopilada enumerada anteriormente para crear un perfil o resumen sobre, por ejemplo, las preferencias y características de un individuo.

NO

L. Información personal sensible

NO


Usaremos y conservaremos la información personal recopilada según sea necesario para proporcionar los Servicios o para:
Categoría B - Siempre que el usuario tenga una cuenta con nosotros
También podemos recopilar otra información personal fuera de estas categorías a través de instancias en las que interactúa con nosotros en persona, en línea, por teléfono o por correo en el contexto de:
Recibir ayuda a través de nuestros canales de atención al cliente;
Participación en encuestas o concursos de clientes; y
Facilitación en la prestación de nuestros Servicios y para responder a sus consultas.
¿Cómo utilizamos y compartimos su información personal?

Conozca cómo utilizamos su información personal en la sección "¿CÓMO PROCESAMOS SU INFORMACIÓN?"

¿Se compartirá su información con alguien más?

Podemos divulgar su información personal a nuestros proveedores de servicios de conformidad con un contrato escrito entre nosotros y cada proveedor de servicios. Obtenga más información sobre cómo divulgamos información personal en la sección "¿CUÁNDO Y CON QUIÉN COMPARTIMOS SU INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL?"

Podemos utilizar su información personal para nuestros propios fines comerciales, como por ejemplo para realizar investigaciones internas para el desarrollo y demostración tecnológicos. Esto no se considera "venta" de su información personal.

No hemos revelado, vendido ni compartido ninguna información personal a terceros con fines comerciales o de negocios en los doce (12) meses anteriores. No venderemos ni compartiremos información personal en el futuro perteneciente a los visitantes, usuarios y otros consumidores del sitio web.

Residentes de California

La Sección 1798.83 del Código Civil de California, también conocida como la ley "Shine The Light", permite a nuestros usuarios residentes de California solicitarnos y obtener de nosotros, una vez al año y de forma gratuita, información sobre categorías de información personal (si corresponde) que divulgamos. a terceros con fines de marketing directo y los nombres y direcciones de todos los terceros con los que compartimos información personal en el año calendario inmediatamente anterior. Si es residente de California y desea realizar dicha solicitud, envíenosla por escrito utilizando la información de contacto que se proporciona a continuación.

Si es menor de 18 años, reside en California y tiene una cuenta registrada en los Servicios, tiene derecho a solicitar la eliminación de los datos no deseados que publique públicamente en los Servicios. Para solicitar la eliminación de dichos datos, comuníquese con nosotros utilizando la información de contacto que se proporciona a continuación e incluya la dirección de correo electrónico asociada con su cuenta y una declaración de que reside en California. Nos aseguraremos de que los datos no se muestren públicamente en los Servicios, pero tenga en cuenta que es posible que los datos no se eliminen completa o completamente de todos nuestros sistemas (por ejemplo, copias de seguridad, etc.).

Aviso de privacidad CCPA

Esta sección se aplica únicamente a los residentes de California. Según la Ley de Privacidad del Consumidor de California (CCPA), usted tiene los derechos que se enumeran a continuación.

El Código de Regulaciones de California define "residentes" como:

(1) toda persona que se encuentre en el Estado de California para fines que no sean temporales o transitorios y
(2) toda persona física domiciliada en el Estado de California que se encuentre fuera del Estado de California por un propósito temporal o transitorio

Todos los demás individuos se definen como "no residentes".

si esto de La definición de "residente" se aplica a usted, debemos cumplir con ciertos derechos y obligaciones con respecto a su información personal.

Tus derechos con respecto a tus datos personales

Derecho a solicitar la supresión de los datos — Solicitud de supresión

Puede solicitar la eliminación de su información personal. Si nos solicita que eliminemos su información personal, respetaremos su solicitud y eliminaremos su información personal, sujeto a ciertas excepciones previstas por la ley, como (pero no limitado a) el ejercicio por parte de otro consumidor de su derecho a la libertad de expresión. , nuestros requisitos de cumplimiento resultantes de una obligación legal o cualquier procesamiento que pueda ser necesario para proteger contra actividades ilegales.

Derecho a ser informado — Solicitud de información

Dependiendo de las circunstancias, usted tiene derecho a saber:
si recopilamos y utilizamos su información personal;
las categorías de información personal que recopilamos;
los fines para los cuales se utiliza la información personal recopilada;
si vendemos o compartimos información personal con terceros;
las categorías de información personal que vendimos, compartimos o divulgamos con fines comerciales;
las categorías de terceros a quienes se vendió, compartió o divulgó la información personal con fines comerciales;
el propósito empresarial o comercial para recopilar, vender o compartir información personal; y
las piezas específicas de información personal que recopilamos sobre usted.
De acuerdo con la ley aplicable, no estamos obligados a proporcionar ni eliminar información del consumidor que no esté identificada en respuesta a una solicitud del consumidor ni a volver a identificar datos individuales para verificar una solicitud del consumidor.

Derecho a la no discriminación por el ejercicio de los derechos de privacidad del consumidor

No lo discriminaremos si ejerce sus derechos de privacidad.

Derecho a limitar el uso y la divulgación de información personal confidencial

No procesamos información personal sensible del consumidor.

Proceso de verificación

Al recibir su solicitud, necesitaremos verificar su identidad para determinar que es la misma persona sobre la cual tenemos información en nuestro sistema. Estos esfuerzos de verificación requieren que le pidamos que proporcione información para que podamos compararla con la información que nos ha proporcionado anteriormente. Por ejemplo, dependiendo del tipo de solicitud que envíe, podemos pedirle que proporcione cierta información para que podamos comparar la información que proporciona con la información que ya tenemos registrada, o podemos comunicarnos con usted a través de un método de comunicación (por ejemplo, teléfono o correo electrónico) que nos hayas facilitado previamente. También podemos utilizar otros métodos de verificación según lo dicten las circunstancias.

Solo utilizaremos la información personal proporcionada en su solicitud para verificar su identidad o autoridad para realizar la solicitud. En la medida de lo posible, evitaremos solicitarle información adicional con fines de verificación. Sin embargo, si no podemos verificar su identidad a partir de la información que ya mantenemos, podemos solicitarle que proporcione información adicional con el fin de verificar su identidad y con fines de seguridad o prevención de fraude. Eliminaremos dicha información proporcionada adicionalmente tan pronto como terminemos de verificarlo.

Otros derechos de privacidad
Puede oponerse al procesamiento de su información personal.
Puede solicitar la corrección de sus datos personales si son incorrectos o ya no son relevantes, o solicitar restringir el procesamiento de la información.
Puede designar a un agente autorizado para realizar una solicitud en virtud de la CCPA en su nombre. Podemos rechazar una solicitud de un agente autorizado que no presente pruebas de que ha sido autorizado válidamente para actuar en su nombre de conformidad con la CCPA.
Puede solicitar la exclusión voluntaria de la venta o el intercambio futuro de su información personal con terceros. Al recibir una solicitud de exclusión voluntaria, actuaremos en consecuencia lo antes posible, pero a más tardar quince (15) días a partir de la fecha de envío de la solicitud.
Para ejercer estos derechos, puede contactarnos visitando , enviando un mensaje de texto a un administrador en Ruby o consultando los detalles de contacto al final de este documento. Si tiene una queja sobre cómo manejamos sus datos, nos gustaría saber de usted.

10. ¿ACTUALIZAMOS ESTE AVISO?

En resumen: Sí, actualizaremos este aviso según sea necesario para cumplir con las leyes pertinentes.

Es posible que actualicemos este aviso de privacidad de vez en cuando. La versión actualizada se indicará mediante una fecha "Revisada" actualizada y la versión actualizada entrará en vigor tan pronto como esté accesible. Si realizamos cambios sustanciales en este aviso de privacidad, podemos notificarle publicando de manera destacada un aviso de dichos cambios o enviándole directamente una notificación. Le recomendamos que revise este aviso de privacidad con frecuencia para estar informado sobre cómo protegemos su información.

11. ¿CÓMO PUEDE CONTACTARNOS SOBRE ESTE AVISO?

Si tiene preguntas o comentarios sobre este aviso, puede enviarnos un correo electrónico a un administrador de Ruby en la aplicación o en el servidor de Discord o contactarnos por correo postal a:

ruby network
123 CALLE DE RUBÍ
124 CALLE DE RUBÍ
Estados Unidos, Nueva York 53842
Estados Unidos

12. ¿CÓMO PUEDES REVISAR, ACTUALIZAR O ELIMINAR LOS DATOS QUE RECOPILAMOS DE TI?

Tiene derecho a solicitar acceso a la información personal que recopilamos de usted, cambiar esa información o eliminarla. Para solicitar revisar, actualizar o eliminar su información personal, visite: .]]>

         </sub_text>

      </texts>

      <type>NINTENDO-NETWORK-EULA</type>

      <version>0300</version>

   </agreement>

   <agreement>

      <country>US</country>

      <language>en</language>

      <language_name>Français</language_name>

      <publish_date>2014-09-29T20:07:35</publish_date>

      <texts

         xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="chunkedStoredAgreementText">

         <main_title>

            <![CDATA[Ruby Network Services Agreement]]>

         </main_title>

         <agree_text>

            <![CDATA[J'accepte]]>

         </agree_text>

         <non_agree_text>

            <![CDATA[Je décline]]>

         </non_agree_text>

         <main_text index="1">

            <![CDATA[CONTRAT DE LICENCE DE L'UTILISATEUR FINAL
Dernière mise à jour : 13/11/23
Cet accord de licence d'utilisateur final (appelé « CLUF ») est un accord juridiquement contraignant
entre vous, le Licencié, un client individuel ou une entité, et Ruby Network, la société,
et l'auteur de Ruby, le logiciel, qui peut inclure des supports associés, des documents imprimés et
documentation en ligne ou électronique. Cet accord est un contrat juridiquement contraignant qui comprend
conditions qui limitent vos droits légaux et la responsabilité des concédants de licence envers vous, et régissent tout accès à et
utilisation du Logiciel. Vous acceptez par la présente, sans limitation ni modification, tous les termes et
conditions contenues dans les présentes.
En installant, copiant ou utilisant autrement le produit (Ruby), le titulaire de licence accepte d'être lié par
les termes et conditions décrits dans le présent CLUF. Toutefois, si le Licencié n'accepte pas les
termes et conditions décrits dans le présent CLUF, ledit titulaire de licence ne peut pas télécharger, installer ou utiliser
Rubis.
Définitions
  « CLUF » fait référence au présent Contrat de licence d'utilisateur final, y compris tout amendement à ce présent
Accord.
« Titulaire de licence » fait référence à la personne ou à l'entité qui télécharge et utilise le Logiciel.
« Concédant de licence » fait référence à la société ou à l'auteur, Ruby Network, située au 1 Road Of The Road,
États-Unis 12345.
  « Logiciel/Produit sous licence » désigne Ruby, le produit sous licence fourni conformément au présent
CLUF.
Octroi de licence
Sous réserve des termes du présent CLUF, Ruby Network accorde par la présente au titulaire de la licence un droit d'auteur,
licence révocable, limitée et non exclusive pendant la durée du présent CLUF pour posséder et utiliser un
copie du Logiciel. Le logiciel est distribué par Ruby Network. Le titulaire de licence n'est pas autorisé
facturer des frais pour la distribution du Logiciel, soit dans un but lucratif, soit simplement pour récupérer des supports et
les coûts de distribution.
Propriété intellectuelle
Par la présente, vous acceptez inconditionnellement que tous les droits, titres et intérêts relatifs aux droits d'auteur et autres
les droits de propriété intellectuelle sur le produit sous licence appartiennent au concédant de licence. Les marques,
les logos, dessins et marques de service apparaissant sur le produit sous licence sont enregistrés et
marques non déposées du concédant de licence. En conséquence, rien dans ce CLUF ou dans le produit sous licence
vous accorde le droit d'utiliser toute forme de propriété intellectuelle contenue dans le produit sous licence.
Par conséquent, tous les droits, titres, intérêts et droits d'auteur relatifs au Logiciel, y compris, mais non
limité à toutes les images, graphiques, animations, audio, vidéo, musique, texte, données, code, algorithme et
informations, sont la propriété du concédant de licence. En conséquence, le Logiciel est protégé par toutes les dispositions applicables
lois sur le droit d'auteur et traités internationaux, et le Licencié est censé utiliser le Logiciel
concernant toute la propriété intellectuelle qui y est contenue, sauf disposition contraire du présent
CLUF.
Description des droits et limitations
Installation et utilisation : le titulaire de la licence peut installer et utiliser le logiciel sur un ordinateur partagé ou
simultanément sur différents ordinateurs et effectuer plusieurs copies de sauvegarde du Logiciel, uniquement à des fins
Utilisation par le Licencié dans le cadre de son activité professionnelle ou personnelle.
Reproduction et distribution : le titulaire de licence ne peut pas dupliquer ou redistribuer des copies du
Logiciel, sans l'autorisation écrite expresse des concédants de licence.
Limitation du titulaire de licence : Le titulaire de licence ne peut pas :
1. Utiliser le Logiciel à des fins autres que personnelles et non commerciales ;
2. Utiliser le logiciel à des fins illégales ou illégales ;
3. Rassemblez du contenu factuel ou toute autre partie du Logiciel par tout moyen automatisé,
y compris, mais sans s'y limiter, le grattage de bases de données ou le grattage d'écran ; ou
4. Effectuer une ingénierie inverse, décompiler ou désassembler le logiciel, sauf et uniquement dans la mesure où
une telle activité est expressément autorisée par la loi applicable malgré la limitation.
Mise à jour et maintenance
Ruby Network fournira des mises à jour et une maintenance sur une base régulière ou selon les besoins.
Soutien
Ruby Network n'a aucune obligation de support logiciel, ni de continuer à fournir ou à mettre à jour l'un des
les logiciels.
Dispositions générales
Résiliation
En cas de résiliation, toutes les licences fournies dans le cadre du présent CLUF prendront immédiatement fin,
et vous acceptez de cesser d'accéder ou de tenter d'accéder à ce produit sous licence.
En conséquence, ce CLUF peut être :
1. Résiliation automatique si le Licencié ne respecte pas l'une des conditions et
conditions en vertu du présent CLUF ;
2. Terminé par Ruby Network ; ou
3. Résilié par le Licencié.
Ruby Network ou le titulaire de la licence peuvent résilier ce CLUF immédiatement sur notification écrite.
à l'autre partie, y compris, mais sans s'y limiter, le courrier électronique.
Non-transférabilité
Le Licencié a la possibilité de transférer définitivement tous les droits en vertu du présent CLUF, à condition que le
le destinataire accepte les termes de ce CLUF. En conséquence, ce CLUF n'est pas cessible ou
transférable par le Licencié sans le consentement écrit préalable de Ruby Network ; et toute tentative
le faire sera nul.
Avis
Tout avis, rapport, approbation ou consentement requis en vertu du présent CLUF doit être écrit et considéré comme
avoir été dûment remis en cas de livraison d par envoi recommandé aux adresses respectives des parties.
L'intégration
Les deux parties conviennent par la présente que ce CLUF constitue la déclaration complète et exclusive et juridique
reconnaissance de la compréhension mutuelle des parties et remplace et annule tout
accord et/ou communication écrit et oral préalable relatif à l'objet de la présente
CLUF.
Divisibilité
Aucun retard ni défaut d'exercice, de la part de l'une ou l'autre des parties, de tout privilège, pouvoir ou droit en vertu du présent
Le CLUF fonctionnera comme une renonciation à l’un des termes et dispositions du présent CLUF. En conséquence, non
l'exercice unique ou partiel de tout droit en vertu du présent Accord empêchera tout exercice ultérieur de tout droit
autre droit en vertu du présent CLUF. Supposons que l'une des dispositions décrites dans ce CLUF soit considérée comme étant
inapplicable ou invalide en tout ou en partie par un tribunal compétent. Dans ce cas, tel
Cette disposition doit être limitée à la mesure minimale nécessaire pour que le présent CLUF reste pleinement en vigueur.
et effet et exécutoire. Les autres dispositions du présent Accord ne seront pas rendues
inapplicable ou invalide. Ils continueront à être exécutoires et valables indépendamment du
dispositions inapplicables et invalides de ce CLUF.
Garantie et clause de non-responsabilité
Ruby Network et l'auteur du logiciel déclinent expressément toute garantie pour Ruby. Le
Le produit sous licence et toute la documentation applicable sont fournis tels quels, sans garantie d'aucune sorte.
qu'elles soient expresses ou implicites, y compris, sans limitation, les garanties implicites de
la qualité marchande, l'adéquation à un usage particulier ou l'absence de contrefaçon. En conséquence, le titulaire
accepte tout risque découlant de l’utilisation ou de la performance du Logiciel.
Responsabilité limitée
Le Licencié accepte que Ruby Network ne soit pas responsable envers le Licencié, ou tout autre
personne ou entité réclamant une perte de profits, de revenus, d'épargne ou toute autre conséquence,
dommages accessoires, spéciaux, punitifs, directs ou indirects, qu'ils découlent d'un contrat, d'un délit, d'une garantie,
ou autrement. Même si Ruby Network a été informé de la possibilité de tels dommages. Ces
les limitations s’appliqueront nécessairement quel que soit l’objectif principal de tout recours limité. Sous
en aucun cas Ruby Network ne peut associer la responsabilité du Licencié ou de toute autre personne ou
l'entité réclamant par l'intermédiaire du Licencié, dépasse le montant monétaire réel payé par le Licencié à
Ruby Network pour le logiciel.
Indemnité
Vous acceptez par la présente d'indemniser et de dégager Ruby Network de toute responsabilité concernant toutes les responsabilités,
dommages, pertes ou dépenses, y compris, mais sans s'y limiter, un avocat raisonnable ou un autre professionnel
les frais liés à toute réclamation, demande, action ou procédure initiée par un tiers contre Ruby Network,
découlant de l'un de vos actes, y compris, sans limitation, la violation du présent CLUF ou de tout autre
accord ou toute loi applicable.
Accord complet
Cet accord constitue à juste titre l'intégralité de l'accord entre le réseau Ruby et le
Licencié et toutes les parties impliquées. Il remplace tous les accords antérieurs des parties, qu'ils soient écrits
ou orale, expresse ou implicite, déclaration, condition, ou représentation ou garantie.
Loi applicable et juridiction
Ce CLUF sera réputé être interprété sous la juridiction des tribunaux situés aux États-Unis,
sans égard aux conflits de lois quant à leurs dispositions. Toute action en justice relative à
ce CLUF sera porté exclusivement devant les tribunaux des États-Unis, et toutes les parties consentent au
juridiction de celui-ci. De plus, la partie gagnante dans toute action visant à faire respecter le présent CLUF sera
a le droit de recouvrer les frais et dépenses, y compris, sans s’y limiter, les frais juridiques. En conséquence, ceci
Le CLUF est rédigé sous la juridiction exclusive des États-Unis et sa juridiction prévaut sur
toute autre juridiction de l'élection de l'un ou l'autre parti. ]]>

         </main_text>

         <sub_title>

            <![CDATA[Privacy Policy]]>

         </sub_title>

         <sub_text index="1">

            <![CDATA[POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ

Dernière mise à jour le 13 novembre 2023



Cet avis de confidentialité pour Ruby Network (« nous », « notre » ou « notre ») décrit comment et pourquoi nous pouvons collecter, stocker, utiliser et/ou partager (« traiter ») vos informations lorsque vous utilisez nos services ( « Services »), par exemple lorsque vous :
Visitez notre site Web sur Ruby Account Server ou l'un de nos sites Web qui renvoie à cet avis de confidentialité.
Interagissez avec nous par d'autres moyens connexes, y compris par des ventes, du marketing ou des événements.
Questions ou préoccupations? La lecture de cet avis de confidentialité vous aidera à comprendre vos droits et vos choix en matière de confidentialité. Si vous n'êtes pas d'accord avec nos politiques et pratiques, veuillez ne pas utiliser nos services. Si vous avez encore des questions ou des préoccupations, veuillez nous contacter à DISCORD.


RÉSUMÉ DES POINTS CLÉS

Ce résumé fournit les points clés de notre avis de confidentialité, mais vous pouvez trouver plus de détails sur l'un de ces sujets en cliquant sur le lien suivant chaque point clé ou en utilisant notre table des matières ci-dessous pour trouver la section que vous recherchez.

Quelles informations personnelles traitons-nous ? Lorsque vous visitez, utilisez ou naviguez sur nos Services, nous pouvons traiter des informations personnelles en fonction de la manière dont vous interagissez avec nous et les Services, des choix que vous faites et des produits et fonctionnalités que vous utilisez. Apprenez-en davantage sur les informations personnelles que vous nous divulguez.

Traitons-nous des informations personnelles sensibles ? Nous ne traitons pas d'informations personnelles sensibles.

Recevons-nous des informations de tiers ? Nous ne recevons aucune information de tiers.

Comment traitons-nous vos informations ? Nous traitons vos informations pour fournir, améliorer et administrer nos services, communiquer avec vous, pour des raisons de sécurité et de prévention de la fraude, et pour nous conformer à la loi. Nous pouvons également traiter vos informations à d'autres fins avec votre consentement. Nous traitons vos informations uniquement lorsque nous avons une raison légale valable de le faire. Apprenez-en davantage sur la manière dont nous traitons vos informations.

Dans quelles situations et avec quelles parties partageons-nous des informations personnelles ? Nous pouvons partager des informations dans des situations spécifiques et avec des tiers spécifiques. Apprenez-en davantage sur quand et avec qui nous partageons vos informations personnelles.

Comment protégeons-nous vos informations ? Nous avons mis en place des processus et procédures organisationnels et techniques pour protéger vos informations personnelles. Cependant, aucune transmission électronique sur Internet ou aucune technologie de stockage d'informations ne peut être garantie comme étant sécurisée à 100 %, nous ne pouvons donc pas promettre ou garantir que les pirates informatiques, les cybercriminels ou d'autres tiers non autorisés ne seront pas en mesure de mettre en échec notre sécurité et de collecter, d'accéder de manière inappropriée. , voler ou modifier vos informations. Apprenez-en davantage sur la manière dont nous protégeons vos informations.

Quels sont vos droits ? Selon l'endroit où vous vous trouvez géographiquement, la loi applicable en matière de confidentialité peut signifier que vous disposez de certains droits concernant vos informations personnelles. Apprenez-en davantage sur vos droits en matière de confidentialité.

Comment exercer vos droits ? Le moyen le plus simple d'exercer vos droits est de visiter , ou de nous contacter. Nous examinerons et répondrons à toute demande conformément aux lois applicables en matière de protection des données.

Vous souhaitez en savoir plus sur ce que nous faisons avec les informations que nous collectons ? Consultez l’avis de confidentialité dans son intégralité.


TABLE DES MATIÈRES

1. QUELLES INFORMATIONS COLLECTONS-NOUS ?
2. COMMENT TRAITONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS ?
3. SUR QUELLES BASES JURIDIQUES NOUS APPUYONS POUR TRAITER VOS INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES ?
4. QUAND ET AVEC QUI PARTAGEONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES ?
5. COMBIEN DE TEMPS CONSERVONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS ?
6. COMMENT GARDONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS EN SÉCURITÉ ?
7. QUELS SONT VOS DROITS À LA VIE PRIVÉE ?
8. COMMANDES POUR LES FONCTIONNALITÉS NE PAS SUIVI
9. LES RÉSIDENTS DES ÉTATS-UNIS ONT-ILS DES DROITS SPÉCIFIQUES À LA VIE PRIVÉE ?
10. Devons-nous mettre à jour cet avis ?
11. COMMENT POUVEZ-VOUS NOUS CONTACTER AU SUJET DE CET AVIS ?
12. COMMENT POUVEZ-VOUS CONSULTER, METTRE À JOUR OU SUPPRIMER LES DONNÉES QUE NOUS COLLECTONS CHEZ VOUS ?


1. QUELLES INFORMATIONS COLLECTONS-NOUS ?

Informations personnelles que vous nous divulguez

En bref : Nous collectons les informations personnelles que vous nous fournissez.

Nous collectons les informations personnelles que vous nous fournissez volontairement lorsque vous vous inscrivez sur les Services, exprimez votre intérêt à obtenir des informations sur nous ou sur nos produits et Services, lorsque vous participez à des activités sur les Services, ou autrement lorsque vous nous contactez.

Informations personnelles fournies par vous. Les informations personnelles que nous collectons dépendent du contexte de vos interactions avec nous et les Services, des choix que vous faites et des produits et fonctionnalités que vous utilisez. Les informations personnelles que nous collectons peuvent inclure les éléments suivants :
noms d'utilisateur
mots de passe
adresses mail
Information sensible. Nous ne traitons pas d'informations sensibles.

Toutes les informations personnelles que vous nous fournissez doivent être véridiques, complètes et exactes, et vous devez nous informer de toute modification apportée à ces informations personnelles.

2. COMMENT TRAITONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS ?

En bref : nous traitons vos informations pour fournir, améliorer et administrer nos services, communiquer avec vous, pour des raisons de sécurité et de prévention de la fraude, et pour nous conformer à la loi. Nous pouvons également traiter vos informations à d'autres fins avec votre consentement.

Nous traiter vos informations personnelles pour diverses raisons, en fonction de la manière dont vous interagissez avec nos Services, notamment :
Pour faciliter la création et l'authentification de comptes et autrement gérer les comptes d'utilisateurs. Nous pouvons traiter vos informations afin que vous puissiez créer et vous connecter à votre compte, ainsi que maintenir votre compte en état de fonctionnement.




Sauver ou protéger les intérêts vitaux d’un individu. Nous pouvons traiter vos informations lorsque cela est nécessaire pour sauvegarder ou protéger les intérêts vitaux d’un individu, par exemple pour éviter tout préjudice.

3. SUR QUELLES BASES JURIDIQUES NOUS APPUYONS POUR TRAITER VOS INFORMATIONS ?

En bref : Nous traitons vos informations personnelles uniquement lorsque nous pensons que cela est nécessaire et que nous avons une raison juridique valable (c'est-à-dire une base légale) pour le faire en vertu de la loi applicable, comme avec votre consentement, pour nous conformer aux lois, pour vous fournir des services. pour conclure ou remplir nos obligations contractuelles, pour protéger vos droits ou pour répondre à nos intérêts commerciaux légitimes.

Si vous résidez dans l'UE ou au Royaume-Uni, cette section s'applique à vous.

Le Règlement général sur la protection des données (RGPD) et le RGPD britannique nous obligent à expliquer les bases juridiques valides sur lesquelles nous nous appuyons pour traiter vos informations personnelles. À ce titre, nous pouvons nous appuyer sur les bases juridiques suivantes pour traiter vos informations personnelles :
Consentement. Nous pouvons traiter vos informations si vous nous avez donné la permission (c'est-à-dire votre consentement) d'utiliser vos informations personnelles dans un but spécifique. Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment. Apprenez-en davantage sur le retrait de votre consentement.
Obligations légales. Nous pouvons traiter vos informations lorsque nous pensons que cela est nécessaire au respect de nos obligations légales, par exemple pour coopérer avec un organisme chargé de l'application de la loi ou un organisme de réglementation, exercer ou défendre nos droits légaux, ou divulguer vos informations comme preuve dans un litige dans lequel nous sommes. impliqué.
Intérêts vitaux. Nous pouvons traiter vos informations lorsque nous estimons que cela est nécessaire pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux ou les intérêts vitaux d'un tiers, par exemple dans des situations impliquant des menaces potentielles pour la sécurité de toute personne.

Si vous résidez au Canada, cette section s'applique à vous.

Nous pouvons traiter vos informations si vous nous avez donné une autorisation spécifique (c'est-à-dire un consentement exprès) pour utiliser vos informations personnelles dans un but spécifique, ou dans des situations où votre autorisation peut être déduite (c'est-à-dire un consentement implicite). Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment.

Dans certains cas exceptionnels, nous pouvons être légalement autorisés, en vertu de la loi applicable, à traiter vos informations sans votre consentement, notamment :
Si la collecte est clairement dans l’intérêt d’une personne et que le consentement ne peut être obtenu en temps opportun
Pour les enquêtes, la détection et la prévention des fraudes
Pour les transactions commerciales sous certaines conditions
S'il est contenu dans une déclaration de témoin et que la collecte est nécessaire pour évaluer, traiter ou régler une réclamation d'assurance
Pour identifier les personnes blessées, malades ou décédées et communiquer avec leurs plus proches parents
Si nous avons des motifs raisonnables de croire qu'une personne a été, est ou pourrait être victime d'exploitation financière
S'il est raisonnable de s'attendre à ce que la collecte et l'utilisation avec consentement compromettent la disponibilité ou l'exactitude des renseignements et que la collecte est raisonnable à des fins liées à une enquête sur une violation d'un accord ou une contravention aux lois du Canada ou d'une province.
Si la divulgation est requise pour se conformer à une assignation à comparaître, un mandat, une ordonnance du tribunal ou des règles du tribunal relatives à la production de dossiers
Si elles ont été produites par un individu dans le cadre de son emploi, de son entreprise ou de sa profession et que la collecte est conforme aux fins pour lesquelles les informations ont été produites
Si la collection est uniquement à des fins journalistiques, artistiques ou littéraires
Si les informations sont accessibles au public et sont spécifiées par la réglementation

4. QUAND ET AVEC QUI PARTAGEONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES ?

En bref : nous pouvons partager des informations dans des situations spécifiques décrites dans cette section et/ou avec les tiers suivants.

Nous pouvons être amenés à partager vos informations personnelles dans les situations suivantes :
Transferts d'entreprises. Nous pouvons partager ou transférer vos informations dans le cadre ou pendant les négociations de toute fusion, vente d'actifs de l'entreprise, financement ou acquisition de tout ou partie de notre entreprise à une autre société.

5. COMBIEN DE TEMPS CONSERVONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS ?

En bref : nous conservons vos informations aussi longtemps que nécessaire pour atteindre les objectifs décrits dans le présent avis de confidentialité, sauf disposition contraire de la loi.

Nous ne conserverons vos informations personnelles que le temps nécessaire aux fins énoncées dans le présent avis de confidentialité, à moins qu'une période de conservation plus longue ne soit requise ou autorisée par la loi (telle que la fiscalité, la comptabilité ou d'autres exigences légales). Aucun objectif de cet avis ne nous obligera à conserver vos informations personnelles plus longtemps que la période pendant laquelle les utilisateurs ont un compte chez nous.

Lorsque nous n'avons aucun besoin professionnel légitime et continu de traiter vos informations personnelles, nous le ferons Nous supprimerons ou anonymiserons ces informations ou, si cela n'est pas possible (par exemple, parce que vos informations personnelles ont été stockées dans des archives de sauvegarde), nous stockerons vos informations personnelles en toute sécurité et les isolerons de tout traitement ultérieur jusqu'à ce que leur suppression soit possible.

6. COMMENT GARDONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS EN SÉCURITÉ ?

En bref : Nous visons à protéger vos informations personnelles grâce à un système de mesures de sécurité organisationnelles et techniques.

Nous avons mis en œuvre des mesures de sécurité techniques et organisationnelles appropriées et raisonnables conçues pour protéger la sécurité de toutes les informations personnelles que nous traitons. Cependant, malgré nos mesures de protection et nos efforts pour sécuriser vos informations, aucune transmission électronique sur Internet ni aucune technologie de stockage d'informations ne peuvent être garanties comme étant sécurisées à 100 %. Nous ne pouvons donc pas promettre ou garantir que les pirates informatiques, les cybercriminels ou d'autres tiers non autorisés ne seront pas en mesure de mettre en péril notre sécurité et de collecter, accéder, voler ou modifier de manière inappropriée vos informations. Bien que nous fassions de notre mieux pour protéger vos informations personnelles, la transmission des informations personnelles vers et depuis nos Services se fait à vos propres risques. Vous ne devez accéder aux Services que dans un environnement sécurisé.

7. QUELS SONT VOS DROITS À LA VIE PRIVÉE ?

En bref : dans certaines régions, telles que l'Espace économique européen (EEE), le Royaume-Uni (UK), la Suisse et le Canada, vous disposez de droits qui vous permettent un meilleur accès et un meilleur contrôle sur vos informations personnelles. Vous pouvez consulter, modifier ou résilier votre compte à tout moment.

Dans certaines régions (comme l'EEE, le Royaume-Uni, la Suisse et le Canada), vous disposez de certains droits en vertu des lois applicables en matière de protection des données. Ceux-ci peuvent inclure le droit (i) de demander l’accès et d’obtenir une copie de vos informations personnelles, (ii) de demander la rectification ou l’effacement ; (iii) pour restreindre le traitement de vos informations personnelles ; (iv) le cas échéant, à la portabilité des données ; et (v) ne pas être soumis à une prise de décision automatisée. Dans certaines circonstances, vous pouvez également avoir le droit de vous opposer au traitement de vos informations personnelles. Vous pouvez faire une telle demande en nous contactant en utilisant les coordonnées fournies dans la section « COMMENT POUVEZ-VOUS NOUS CONTACTER À PROPOS DE CET AVIS ? ci-dessous.

Nous examinerons et répondrons à toute demande conformément aux lois applicables en matière de protection des données.
 
Si vous résidez dans l'EEE ou au Royaume-Uni et que vous pensez que nous traitons illégalement vos informations personnelles, vous avez également le droit de porter plainte auprès de l'autorité de protection des données de votre État membre ou de l'autorité de protection des données du Royaume-Uni.

Si vous résidez en Suisse, vous pouvez contacter le Préposé fédéral à la protection des données et à la transparence.

Retrait de votre consentement : Si nous comptons sur votre consentement pour traiter vos informations personnelles, qui peut être un consentement exprès et/ou implicite selon la loi applicable, vous avez le droit de retirer votre consentement à tout moment. Vous pouvez retirer votre consentement à tout moment en nous contactant en utilisant les coordonnées fournies dans la section « COMMENT POUVEZ-VOUS NOUS CONTACTER À PROPOS DE CET AVIS ? ci-dessous ou en mettant à jour vos préférences.

Cependant, veuillez noter que cela n’affectera pas la licéité du traitement avant son retrait ni, lorsque la loi applicable le permet, que cela n’affectera le traitement de vos informations personnelles effectué sur la base de motifs de traitement licites autres que le consentement.

Information sur le compte

Si vous souhaitez à tout moment consulter ou modifier les informations de votre compte ou résilier votre compte, vous pouvez :
Connectez-vous aux paramètres de votre compte et mettez à jour votre compte utilisateur.
À votre demande de résiliation de votre compte, nous désactiverons ou supprimerons votre compte et vos informations de nos bases de données actives. Cependant, nous pouvons conserver certaines informations dans nos fichiers pour prévenir la fraude, résoudre des problèmes, faciliter toute enquête, faire respecter nos conditions légales et/ou nous conformer aux exigences légales applicables.

Si vous avez des questions ou des commentaires sur vos droits à la vie privée, vous pouvez nous envoyer un e-mail à DISCORD.

8. COMMANDES POUR LES FONCTIONNALITÉS NE PAS SUIVI

La plupart des navigateurs Web et certains systèmes d'exploitation mobiles et applications mobiles incluent une fonctionnalité ou un paramètre Do-Not-Track (« DNT ») que vous pouvez activer pour signaler votre préférence en matière de confidentialité afin que les données sur vos activités de navigation en ligne ne soient pas surveillées et collectées. À ce stade, aucune norme technologique uniforme pour la reconnaissance et la mise en œuvre des signaux DNT n’a été finalisée. En tant que tel, nous ne répondons pas actuellement aux signaux du navigateur DNT ou à tout autre mécanisme communiquant automatiquement votre choix de ne pas être suivi en ligne. Si une norme de suivi en ligne que nous devons suivre à l'avenir est adoptée, nous vous informerons de cette pratique dans une version révisée de cet avis de confidentialité.

9. LES RÉSIDENTS DES ÉTATS-UNIS ONT-ILS DES DROITS SPÉCIFIQUES À LA VIE PRIVÉE ?

En bref : si vous résidez en Californie, vous bénéficiez de droits spécifiques concernant l'accès à vos informations personnelles.

Quelles catégories d’informations personnelles collectons-nous ?

Nous avons collecté les catégories suivantes d'informations personnelles dans au cours des douze (12) derniers mois :

Exemples de catégories collectés
A. Identifiants
Coordonnées, telles que nom réel, pseudonyme, adresse postale, numéro de téléphone ou de mobile, identifiant personnel unique, identifiant en ligne, adresse de protocole Internet, adresse e-mail et nom de compte

NON

B. Informations personnelles telles que définies dans la loi californienne sur les dossiers clients
Nom, coordonnées, formation, emploi, antécédents professionnels et informations financières

NON

C. Caractéristiques de classification protégées en vertu de la loi nationale ou fédérale
Sexe et date de naissance

NON

D. Informations commerciales
Informations sur les transactions, historique des achats, détails financiers et informations de paiement

NON

E. Informations biométriques
Empreintes digitales et empreintes vocales

NON

F. Internet ou autre activité réseau similaire
Historique de navigation, historique de recherche, comportement en ligne, données d'intérêt et interactions avec nos sites Web, applications, systèmes et publicités ainsi qu'avec d'autres.

NON

G. Données de géolocalisation
Emplacement de l'appareil

NON

H. Informations audio, électroniques, visuelles, thermiques, olfactives ou similaires
Images et enregistrements audio, vidéo ou d'appels créés dans le cadre de nos activités commerciales

NON

I. Informations professionnelles ou liées à l'emploi
Coordonnées professionnelles afin de vous fournir nos services au niveau de l'entreprise ou titre du poste, antécédents professionnels et qualifications professionnelles si vous postulez pour un emploi chez nous.

NON

J.Informations sur l'éducation
Dossiers des étudiants et informations d'annuaire

NON

K. Inférences tirées des informations personnelles collectées
Inférences tirées de l'une des informations personnelles collectées répertoriées ci-dessus pour créer un profil ou un résumé sur, par exemple, les préférences et les caractéristiques d'un individu.

NON

L. Informations personnelles sensibles

NON


Nous utiliserons et conserverons les informations personnelles collectées selon les besoins pour fournir les Services ou pour :
Catégorie B - Tant que l'utilisateur dispose d'un compte chez nous
Nous pouvons également collecter d'autres informations personnelles en dehors de ces catégories dans les cas où vous interagissez avec nous en personne, en ligne, par téléphone ou par courrier dans le contexte de :
Recevoir de l'aide via nos canaux de support client ;
Participation à des enquêtes clients ou à des concours ; et
Facilitation dans la prestation de nos Services et pour répondre à vos demandes.
Comment utilisons-nous et partageons-nous vos informations personnelles ?

Découvrez comment nous utilisons vos informations personnelles dans la section « COMMENT TRAITONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS ? »

Vos informations seront-elles partagées avec quelqu'un d'autre ?

Nous pouvons divulguer vos informations personnelles à nos prestataires de services conformément à un contrat écrit entre nous et chaque prestataire de services. Apprenez-en davantage sur la manière dont nous divulguons vos informations personnelles dans la section « QUAND ET AVEC QUI PARTAGEONS-NOUS VOS INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES ? »

Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations personnelles à nos propres fins commerciales, par exemple pour entreprendre des recherches internes à des fins de développement et de démonstration technologiques. Ceci n’est pas considéré comme une « vente » de vos informations personnelles.

Nous n'avons divulgué, vendu ou partagé aucune information personnelle à des tiers à des fins commerciales au cours des douze (12) mois précédents. Nous ne vendrons ni ne partagerons à l’avenir des informations personnelles appartenant aux visiteurs du site Web, aux utilisateurs et à d’autres consommateurs.

Résidents de Californie

L'article 1798.83 du Code civil de Californie, également connu sous le nom de loi « Shine The Light », permet à nos utilisateurs résidant en Californie de demander et d'obtenir de notre part, une fois par an et gratuitement, des informations sur les catégories d'informations personnelles (le cas échéant) que nous avons divulguées. à des tiers à des fins de marketing direct ainsi que les noms et adresses de tous les tiers avec lesquels nous avons partagé des informations personnelles au cours de l'année civile précédente. Si vous résidez en Californie et souhaitez faire une telle demande, veuillez nous soumettre votre demande par écrit en utilisant les coordonnées fournies ci-dessous.

Si vous avez moins de 18 ans, résidez en Californie et disposez d'un compte enregistré auprès des Services, vous avez le droit de demander la suppression des données indésirables que vous publiez publiquement sur les Services. Pour demander la suppression de ces données, veuillez nous contacter en utilisant les informations de contact fournies ci-dessous et inclure l'adresse e-mail associée à votre compte et une déclaration indiquant que vous résidez en Californie. Nous veillerons à ce que les données ne soient pas affichées publiquement sur les Services, mais sachez que les données ne peuvent pas être complètement ou totalement supprimées de tous nos systèmes (par exemple, sauvegardes, etc.).

Avis de confidentialité du CCPA

Cette section s'applique uniquement aux résidents de Californie. En vertu du California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), vous disposez des droits énumérés ci-dessous.

Le Code de réglementation de la Californie définit un « résident » comme suit :

(1) toute personne qui se trouve dans l’État de Californie à des fins autres que temporaires ou transitoires et
(2) toute personne physique domiciliée dans l'État de Californie qui se trouve en dehors de l'État de Californie à des fins temporaires ou transitoires

Toutes les autres personnes sont définies comme des « non-résidents ».

Si ce de La finition de « résident » s'applique à vous, nous devons respecter certains droits et obligations concernant vos renseignements personnels.

Vos droits concernant vos données personnelles

Droit de demander la suppression des données — Demande de suppression

Vous pouvez demander la suppression de vos informations personnelles. Si vous nous demandez de supprimer vos informations personnelles, nous respecterons votre demande et supprimerons vos informations personnelles, sous réserve de certaines exceptions prévues par la loi, telles que (mais sans s'y limiter) l'exercice par un autre consommateur de son droit à la liberté d'expression. , nos exigences de conformité résultant d'une obligation légale, ou tout traitement pouvant être nécessaire pour se protéger contre les activités illégales.

Droit d’être informé — Demander à savoir

Selon les circonstances, vous avez le droit de savoir :
si nous collectons et utilisons vos informations personnelles ;
les catégories d'informations personnelles que nous collectons ;
les finalités pour lesquelles les informations personnelles collectées sont utilisées ;
si nous vendons ou partageons des informations personnelles avec des tiers ;
les catégories d'informations personnelles que nous avons vendues, partagées ou divulguées à des fins commerciales ;
les catégories de tiers auxquels les informations personnelles ont été vendues, partagées ou divulguées à des fins commerciales ;
l'objectif commercial ou commercial de la collecte, de la vente ou du partage d'informations personnelles ; et
les informations personnelles spécifiques que nous avons collectées à votre sujet.
Conformément à la loi applicable, nous ne sommes pas obligés de fournir ou de supprimer des informations client anonymisées en réponse à une demande du consommateur ou de réidentifier les données individuelles pour vérifier une demande du consommateur.

Droit à la non-discrimination pour l’exercice du droit à la vie privée d’un consommateur

Nous ne ferons aucune discrimination à votre égard si vous exercez vos droits à la vie privée.

Droit de limiter l’utilisation et la divulgation d’informations personnelles sensibles

Nous ne traitons pas les informations personnelles sensibles des consommateurs.

Processus de vérification

Dès réception de votre demande, nous devrons vérifier votre identité pour déterminer que vous êtes la même personne au sujet de laquelle nous avons les informations dans notre système. Ces efforts de vérification nous obligent à vous demander de fournir des informations afin que nous puissions les faire correspondre aux informations que vous nous avez précédemment fournies. Par exemple, selon le type de demande que vous soumettez, nous pouvons vous demander de fournir certaines informations afin que nous puissions faire correspondre les informations que vous fournissez avec les informations que nous avons déjà dans nos dossiers, ou nous pouvons vous contacter via une méthode de communication (par exemple, téléphone ou email) que vous nous avez préalablement fourni. Nous pouvons également utiliser d'autres méthodes de vérification selon les circonstances.

Nous utiliserons uniquement les informations personnelles fournies dans votre demande pour vérifier votre identité ou votre autorité pour faire la demande. Dans la mesure du possible, nous éviterons de vous demander des informations supplémentaires à des fins de vérification. Toutefois, si nous ne pouvons pas vérifier votre identité à partir des informations que nous conservons déjà, nous pouvons vous demander de fournir des informations supplémentaires afin de vérifier votre identité et à des fins de sécurité ou de prévention de la fraude. Nous supprimerons ces informations supplémentaires fournies dès que nous aurons fini de vous vérifier.

Autres droits à la vie privée
Vous pouvez vous opposer au traitement de vos informations personnelles.
Vous pouvez demander la rectification de vos données personnelles si elles sont incorrectes ou ne sont plus pertinentes, ou demander la limitation du traitement des informations.
Vous pouvez désigner un agent autorisé pour faire une demande en vertu de la CCPA en votre nom. Nous pouvons refuser une demande d'un agent autorisé qui ne soumet pas la preuve qu'il a été valablement autorisé à agir en votre nom conformément au CCPA.
Vous pouvez demander à vous désinscrire de la vente ou du partage futur de vos informations personnelles à des tiers. Dès réception d'une demande de désinscription, nous y donnerons suite dès que possible, mais au plus tard quinze (15) jours à compter de la date de soumission de la demande.
Pour exercer ces droits, vous pouvez nous contacter en visitant , en envoyant un message privé à un administrateur sur Ruby , ou en vous référant aux coordonnées au bas de ce document. Si vous avez une plainte concernant la façon dont nous traitons vos données, nous aimerions vous entendre.

10. Devons-nous mettre à jour cet avis ?

En bref : Oui, nous mettrons à jour cet avis si nécessaire pour rester en conformité avec les lois en vigueur.

Nous pouvons mettre à jour cet avis de confidentialité de temps à autre. La version mise à jour sera indiquée par une date de mise à jour « Révisée » et la version mise à jour entrera en vigueur dès qu'elle sera accessible. Si nous apportons des modifications importantes à cet avis de confidentialité, nous pouvons vous en informer soit en affichant bien en vue un avis de ces modifications, soit en vous envoyant directement une notification. Nous vous encourageons à consulter fréquemment cet avis de confidentialité pour être informé de la manière dont nous protégeons vos informations.

11. COMMENT POUVEZ-VOUS NOUS CONTACTER AU SUJET DE CET AVIS ?

Si vous avez des questions ou des commentaires sur cet avis, vous pouvez nous envoyer un e-mail à un administrateur Ruby sur l'application ou le serveur Discord ou nous contacter par courrier à :

Ruby Network
123 RUE DU RUBIS
124 RUE DU RUBIS
États-Unis, New York 53842
États-Unis

12. COMMENT POUVEZ-VOUS CONSULTER, METTRE À JOUR OU SUPPRIMER LES DONNÉES QUE NOUS COLLECTONS CHEZ VOUS ?

Vous avez le droit de demander l’accès aux informations personnelles que nous collectons auprès de vous, de modifier ces informations ou de les supprimer. Pour demander la révision, la mise à jour ou la suppression de vos informations personnelles, veuillez visiter : .]]>

         </sub_text>

      </texts>

      <type>NINTENDO-NETWORK-EULA</type>

      <version>0300</version>

   </agreement>

</agreements>